adclarity.com 2014-06-10

# AdClarity - Media Intelligence Platform

AdClarity is strongly committed to protecting and respecting your privacy rights in accordance with the respective compliance obligations of the countries in which we operate. This AdClarity Customer Privacy Policy sets out the basis on which AdClarity protect visitors' personal data, while understanding our data security and privacy practices regarding storing customers' personal data of AdClarity services.

**Personal identifiable information**

AdClarity collects information from its customers in a fair and lawful manner for the purposes of customer identification, providing services and billing and related administration. AdClarity collects data, such as name, address, e-mail address, fax and telephone numbers, on customers and prospects, through the registration forms on the AdClarity Sales Site. AdClarity may collect other information about customers and prospects use of the website and their business or the company for whom they work, for the purpose of direct marketing campaigns, as permitted by law. Customers and prospects are not obliged to provide such information and may choose to opt out of such direct marketing campaigns through contacting their account representative or customer support email [support@AdClarity.com](mailto:support@AdClarity.com) . AdClarity will give you the option to opt out of each commercial email communication that we may send to you.

AdClarity may keep a record of any correspondence with customers and newsletter subscribers until it is no longer necessary.

AdClarity may also ask you to complete surveys for research purposes and may keep a copy of your responses. Please note that you are not obliged to respond to such surveys.

**Cookies and Log files**

AdClarity may collect information about your computer and browsing preferences, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration purposes. This is statistical data about AdClarity's users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

In some circumstances, AdClarity uses cookies to enhance the functionality of the service we offer our customers. A cookie is a small data file on the hard drive of your computer. AdClarity uses cookies to identify a customer and to store registration details so that the customer is no longer required to re-enter these details on subsequent visits. In addition, AdClarity uses cookies to indicate the number of computers used by each customer to log-in to the AdClarity service, to prevent abuse of the system and logins (See Terms of Use). AdClarity also collects information on IP addresses and web browsers used by customers when they access the service for the same reasons mentioned above. 

**Uses made of the information**

AdClarity uses information held about you in the following ways:  
To provide you with information and services that you request from AdClarity or which AdClarity feels may interest you, where you have consented for such purposes;

  * To carry out its obligations in any contracts with you; 
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of the AdClarity service, when you choose to do so; 
  * To notify you about the changes to the AdClarity service, including new product announcements. 
  * To conduct internal administration of AdClarity's business. 

**Does AdClarity disclose information to Third Parties?**

AdClarity does not share or disclose personal information of its clients, nor any other data type such as personal service usage, personal logs or any other personal data AdClarity stores. AdClarity does not permit third party vendors to use customer personal data for any purpose outside of those disclosed within this privacy policy.  
AdClarity may disclose your personal data to other parties:

  * In the event that AdClarity sells or buys any business or assets, in which case AdClarity may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; 
  * If AdClarity or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; 
  * If AdClarity is under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation; 
  * In order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements with you; 
  * To protect the rights, property or safety of AdClarity or its customers, which includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; 

**Illegal, Unauthorized, or Fraudulent Content or Activities**

The Service may be used only for lawful purposes and in a lawful manner. You agree to comply with all applicable laws and regulations.

AdClarity has the right to monitor any Review, activity, and content associated with the Service. AdClarity may investigate any reported violation of its policies and take any action it deems appropriate, including terminating your access to the Service without notice.

AdClarity may report any activity it suspects violates any law or regulation to appropriate law enforcement officials, regulators, or other third parties. To cooperate with governmental requests, to protect AdClarity's systems and users, to ensure the integrity and operation of AdClarity's business and systems, or in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements, AdClarity may access and disclose any information it considers necessary or appropriate, including user contact details, IP addressing and traffic information, posted content, and Web usage paths. By using the Service you expressly consent to the foregoing use and disclosure. 

**Securing your personal data**

By submitting your personal data to AdClarity, you consent to the transfer and storage of personal data for processing by AdClarity in another country of our choosing. AdClarity will take reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely outside of your country of origin and in accordance with this Customer Privacy Policy.

All information you provide to AdClarity is stored on secure servers. Any payment transaction information will be encrypted and used solely to process the transaction. Where AdClarity has given you a password which enables you to access certain parts of the AdClarity website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.

Once AdClarity has received your information, AdClarity will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

**Changing or deleting secured information**

AdClarity does its utmost to ensure the quality and accuracy of the customer personal data in its possession, and as such invites newsletter subscribers and customers of the service to access or update their details as necessary. AdClarity is committed to providing reasonable and practical access to allow visitors the opportunity to identify and correct any inaccurate details we may hold.

AdClarity shall respond to your data access request within 30 days of receiving your request. If AdClarity is unable to respond to your request within such period AdClarity shall notify you of the reason why AdClarity is so unable.

All customers and prospects have the right to access or update personal data that they have submitted through the AdClarity website. Should subscribers and customers subsequently choose to unsubscribe from mailing lists they can do so by following the instructions on how to unsubscribe provided in all AdClarity communications. On request, AdClarity will delete personally identifiable information that has been submitted from the current database, unless it is required to retain such information by law. 

**Disclaimer of Warranty**

You understand and agree that the service is provided on an "as is" and "as available" basis. You expressly agree that use of this service is at your sole risk.

You acknowledge and agree that any software or other content downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of the service is done at your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible for any damage to your computer system or loss of data that results from the download of such software and/or content. 

**Changes to the Customer Privacy Policy**

Any changes that AdClarity makes to this Customer Privacy Policy shall be posted on the AdClarity website and where appropriate with material changes, we may notify you via email. 

**Contact our Customer Support**

If you have any queries about the privacy statement or to report a privacy issue or wish to know more about our Complaint Handling Procedure please contact our support team at [support@adclarity.com](mailto:support@adclarity.com)
